<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<BLOGGER name="">
    <EMAIL></EMAIL>
    <PASSWORD></PASSWORD>
    <AVATAR></AVATAR>
    <BLOG title="">
    	<ARTICLE>		
      		<TITLE>Fr Ted's Slideshow</TITLE>
		<GENRE>Politcs</GENRE>
		<DATE>28/4/16</DATE>
		<ENTRY>Willkommen.
			Bienvenu.
			It's a great honour and privilege for me to present this celebration of the diverse cultures that exist on Craggy Island.
			Namely, Chinese people and people from Craggy Island.
			I've prepared a short slide presentation which reflects this multicultural mix.
			So, without further ado let's start the show.
		</ENTRY>
		<IMG></IMG>
		<ENTRY>	He visited the Island a few years ago, I forget his name now but I got on very well with him.
			I just thought I'd throw that in.
			Will there be any free drink at this? Yes, a limited supply of free drink afterwards.
		</ENTRY>
		<IMG></IMG>
		<ENTRY>
			The Great Wall Of China, a miracle of Chinese engineering.
			So big you can see it from anywhere in the world.
		</ENTRY>
		<IMG></IMG>
		<ENTRY>	Chairman Mao, secretary of the Communist Party of China, the world's biggest Communist party, and in my view, the best.
		</ENTRY>
		<IMG></IMG>	Mr Miyagi from The karate kid.
		<ENTRY>	My favourite film, not because of the karate kid, but because of Mr Miyagi.
			Every day, I remember some of his many words of wisdom.
		</ENTRY>
		<IMG></IMG>	kato! Where would he spring from next? The Maori.
		<ENTRY>	I'm sorry, I don't know how that got in there.
			Of course, there are no Maoris on Craggy Island.
		</ENTRY>
		<IMG></IMG>
		<ENTRY>Ming the Merciless.
		</ENTRY>
		<IMG></IMG>
		<ENTRY>And best of all, the Chinese people themselves.
		       Look at them, aren't they great? The Chinese.
			A great bunch of lads.
		</ENTRY>
		<IMG></IMG>
		<ENTRY>	I think we've addressed all aspects of Chinese culture and I'd like to thank you all for coming here tonight and if you'd
 			like to, we can have a bit of an old chat.
			Well, the slide show was a big pile of crap.
			But the free drink very much appreciated.
			Thank you, Father Crilly.
			I just wanted to clear things up.
			I'm not a fascist, I'm a priest.
			Fascists dress in black and tell people what to do, whereas priests - More drink! - (Cheers ) 
		</ENTRY>
		<COMMENT>Ha, Ha, I loved that episode!</COMMENT>
		<LIKES>5</LIKES>     	
    	</ARTICLE>
    </BLOG>
</BLOGGER>
